liveanime.net 2011-05-29

# LiveAnime | Privacy Policy

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as the site registration). The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

**1.** It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

**2.** We transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you before the information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Information Gathering and Usage

**1.** When you register for our services, we ask for information such as your name and email address.

**2.** We uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, services improvement, contact, and research.

### Cookies

**1.** A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.

**2.** Cookies are required to login to our services, we use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.

### Data Storage

We use third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run LiveAnime.net. 

### Disclosure

We may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with demands from the authorities or when your actions violate the Terms of Use.

### Changes

We may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to the **LiveAnime Team** via the [Contact form](http://www.liveanime.net/contacts).
